<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NZ Bone Broth - Elevate Wellness, One Sip at a Time on PrimeBroth</title>
    <link>http://localhost:59770/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NZ Bone Broth - Elevate Wellness, One Sip at a Time on PrimeBroth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 13:48:01 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:59770/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Bone Broth for Pets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59770/posts/benefits-of-bonebroth-for-pets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 13:48:01 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59770/posts/benefits-of-bonebroth-for-pets/</guid>
      <description>Bone broth is a stock or broth made by simmering animal bones, such as cattle, chicken, or lamb. The bones are slow-cooked with water for hours to extract nourishing compounds like collagen and essential amino acids that are not found in usual pet food or home-cooked food. Bone broth is often used as a cooking component; however, many people prefer to drink it on its own. For pets, it can be added to their food or used on its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Bone Broth For Dogs in New Zealand (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59770/posts/best-bone-broth-for-dogs-in-new-zealand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:48:01 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59770/posts/best-bone-broth-for-dogs-in-new-zealand/</guid>
      <description>Bone broth is excellent not only for humans but also for pets. It can be used as a meal topper or on its own to replace boring and nutrition-less water. Dogs love their kibble when soaked in the bone broth. Generally, New Zealand has only a few bone broth makers who also provide bone broth for our furry friends, we covered them all here.&#xA;The best bone broth for dogs in New Zealand is beef bone broth from PrimaBroth, venison &amp;amp; goat from Raw Essentials, and Roar classic beef bone broth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken and Vegetable Soup with Bone Broth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59770/posts/chicken-vegetable-soup-with-bone-broth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:48:01 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59770/posts/chicken-vegetable-soup-with-bone-broth/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 4 cups chicken bone broth 2 cups cooked shredded chicken (leftover rotisserie chicken works well) 1 onion, diced 2 carrots, diced 2 celery stalks, diced 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 cup diced tomatoes (canned or fresh) 1 teaspoon dried thyme 1 teaspoon dried oregano Salt and pepper to taste 2 tablespoons olive oil Optional: chopped fresh parsley for garnish Instructions: Sauté Vegetables: In a large pot, heat the olive oil over medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken and Vegetable Soup with Bone Broth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59770/recipes/chicken-vegetable-soup-with-bone-broth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:48:01 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59770/recipes/chicken-vegetable-soup-with-bone-broth/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 4 cups chicken bone broth 2 cups cooked shredded chicken (leftover rotisserie chicken works well) 1 onion, diced 2 carrots, diced 2 celery stalks, diced 2 cloves garlic, minced 1 cup diced tomatoes (canned or fresh) 1 teaspoon dried thyme 1 teaspoon dried oregano Salt and pepper to taste 2 tablespoons olive oil Optional: chopped fresh parsley for garnish Instructions: Sauté Vegetables: In a large pot, heat the olive oil over medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sitemap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:59770/sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:59770/sitemap/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
