<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beef Tallow for Skin NZ on PrimalPantry</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/beef-tallow-for-skin-nz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beef Tallow for Skin NZ on PrimalPantry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 13:05:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/beef-tallow-for-skin-nz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Is Tallow Balm Made? A Look at Ingredients &amp; Process</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-is-tallow-balm-made/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 13:05:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-is-tallow-balm-made/</guid>
      <description>How Is Tallow Balm Made? Tallow balm is a simple but effective moisturizer made from beef tallow, blended with nourishing oils. However, not all tallow balm NZ products are made the same way—quality depends on the ingredients and process used.&#xA;What Is Tallow Balm Made Of? A good tallow balm contains only a few key ingredients:&#xA;Beef tallow (from suet, not dripping) Olive oil – Softens the balm and boosts hydration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Results You Can Expect from Using Tallow Balm on Eczema</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/results-you-can-expect-from-using-tallow-balm-on-eczema/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 13:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/results-you-can-expect-from-using-tallow-balm-on-eczema/</guid>
      <description>Results You Can Expect from Using Tallow Balm on Eczema Tallow balm NZ is known for its deep hydration, soothing properties, and ability to support the skin barrier. But what kind of results should you expect when using it for eczema-prone skin?&#xA;1. Immediate Relief (First Few Uses) ✔ Less itching and irritation → Skin feels calmer and more comfortable.&#xA;✔ Deep hydration → No more tight, dry feeling.&#xA;💡 Many people notice instant moisture retention compared to regular creams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Frankincense in Skincare: A Natural Anti-Aging Ingredient</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/benefits-of-frankincense-in-skincare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 14:50:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/benefits-of-frankincense-in-skincare/</guid>
      <description>Benefits of Frankincense in Skincare Frankincense has been used for centuries in skincare and healing. When added to tallow balm NZ, it boosts skin repair, elasticity, and hydration.&#xA;1. Anti-Aging Properties ✔ Reduces fine lines &amp;amp; wrinkles → Supports collagen production.&#xA;✔ Firms skin → Improves elasticity for a youthful glow.&#xA;💡 Frankincense is known for its skin-tightening effects.&#xA;2. Soothes &amp;amp; Repairs Damaged Skin ✔ Anti-inflammatory → Reduces redness and irritation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Tallow Balm as a Moisturiser: A Natural Alternative to Lotions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-tallow-balm-as-a-moisturiser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-tallow-balm-as-a-moisturiser/</guid>
      <description>Using Tallow Balm as a Moisturiser: A Natural Alternative Tallow balm NZ is one of the best natural alternatives to commercial moisturisers. It hydrates deeply, absorbs quickly, and nourishes without synthetic chemicals.&#xA;Why Use Tallow Balm Instead of Lotion? ✔ Deep Hydration – Locks in moisture for hours, unlike water-based creams.&#xA;✔ Skin-Loving Nutrients – Contains vitamins A, D, E, and K for skin health.&#xA;✔ Non-Greasy &amp;amp; Fast-Absorbing – Doesn’t sit on the skin like petroleum-based creams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does Tallow Balm Go Grainy? (And Why Ours Doesn’t)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-does-tallow-balm-go-grainy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-does-tallow-balm-go-grainy/</guid>
      <description>Why Does Tallow Balm Go Grainy? (And Why Ours Doesn’t) If you’ve used tallow balm NZ, you may have come across some that feel grainy or uneven. It’s a common issue, and people making tallow balms in NZ will often tell you it’s normal. While the balm still works, graininess doesn’t have to happen.&#xA;At PrimalCare, we’ve refined our process to ensure a consistently smooth, whipped texture. And if your balm ever arrives grainy, we’ll refund you—our Grain-Free Guarantee means you never have to settle for rough, uneven balm.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
